Finding Aid for the Colonial Court Records Group, 1665-1787 SR.401
State Archives of North Carolina
- Estate Papers, 1665-1767; SR.401.8; 5.000; Colonial Courts (Box Estate Papers, Adams-Branston, 1665-1767, Box Estate Papers, Brasely-Child, 1665-1767, Box Estate Papers, Church-Eaves, 1665-1767, Box Estate Papers, Edgerton-Haughton, 1665-1767, Box Estate Papers, Hawkins-Hyde, 1665-1767, Box Estate
  - Durant, An, n.d.; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Durant, An)
  - Durant, George, 1696; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Durant, George)
  - Early, William, 1712; CCR 198; Colonial Courts (Folder Early, William)
  - Edgerton, James, 1759; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Edgerton, James)
  - Elenworth, Richard, 1695; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Elenworth, Richard)
  - Elliot, John, 1735; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Elliot, John)
  - Ellis, James, n.d.; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Ellis, James)
  - Ellis, Joseph, 1709; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Ellis, Joseph)
  - Espey, James, 1738-1745; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Espey, James)
  - Etheridge, Richard, 1739-1741; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Etheridge, Richard)
  - Everard, Richard, Sir, 1736; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Everard, Richard, Sir)
  - Everenden, Thomas, 1727-1729; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Everenden, Thomas)
  - Farrah, Francis, 1724-1725; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Farrah, Francis)
  - Fergison, Adam, 1703; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Fergison, Adam)
  - Fewox, James, 1703-1715; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Fewox, James)
  - Finch, Jeremiah, 1723-1731; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Finch, Jeremiah)
  - Finch, Rowland Porter, 1745-1746; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Finch, Rowland Porter)
  - Flemin, James, 1721; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Flemin, James)
  - Flyn, Collumb, 1733-1740; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Flyn, Collumb)
  - Fomvile, Peter, 1721-1723; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Fomvile, Peter)
  - Foy, Francis, 1759-1760; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Foy, Francis)
  - French, Ralph, 1689; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder French, Ralph)
  - Fry, John, 1737-1740; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Fry, John)
  - Fryers, James, 1755; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Fryers, James)
  - Gabourel (Gabriel), Joshua, 1736-1740; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Gabourel (Gabriel), Joshua)
  - Gale, Edmund and Mary (see John Hecklefield), 1740-1744; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Gale, Edmund and Mary (see John Hecklefield))
  - Garland, Peter, 1745; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Garland, Peter)
  - Gambell, Adam, 1702; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Gambell, Adam)
  - George, James, 1742-1743; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder George, James)
  - Gible, Dederith, 1734-1738; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Gible, Dederith)
  - Gibson (Gipson), Charles and Ellenor, 1726-1729; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Gibson (Gipson), Charles and Ellenor)
  - Gilbert, Francis, 1726-1727; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Gilbert, Francis)
  - Giles, Mathias, 1710-1714; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Giles, Mathias)
  - Gillam, Thomas, 1703; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Gillam, Thomas)
  - Gladstaines, George, 1710-1713; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Gladstaines, George)
  - Glover, William, 1707-1723; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Glover, William)
  - Godfrey, Elizabeth and John, 1702-1704; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Godfrey, Elizabeth and John)
  - Godwin, Joseph, 1755-1758; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Godwin, Joseph)
  - Godwin, William, 1756-1757; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Godwin, William)
  - Goodlatt, Alex'd (Alexander), CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Goodlatt, Alex'd (Alexander))
  - Goodman, Thomas, 1726-1740; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Goodman, Thomas)
  - Gordon, Robert, 1736-1737; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Gordon, Robert)
  - Gosnell, ?, n.d.; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Gosnell, ?)
  - Granger, Joshua, 1743-1744; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Granger, Joshua)
  - Gray, William, 1737-1742; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Gray, William)
  - Greer, Archeball, 1696; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Greer, Archeball)
  - Gregory, William, 1753-1754; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Gregory, William)
  - Grills, John, 1741-1742; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Grills, John)
  - Grills, Richard, 1720; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Grills, Richard)
  - Guston, Henry, 1742; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Guston, Henry)
  - Gwin, James, 1736; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Gwin, James)
  - Halsey, Daniel, 1717-1727; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Halsey, Daniel)
  - Hamilton, John, 1723-1724; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Hamilton, John)
  - Harris, David, 1705-1712; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Harris, David)
  - Harris, John, 1710-1726; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Harris, John)
  - Harris, Newell, 1758; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Harris, Newell)
  - Harris, Thomas, n.d.; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Harris, Thomas)
  - Hart, Robert (minor), 1741; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Hart, Robert (minor))
  - Hartley, Francis, Col., 1694-1697; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Hartley, Francis, Col.)
  - Harvey, John, 1690; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Harvey, John)
  - Harvey, Richard, 1733-1743; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Harvey, Richard)
  - Harvey, Thomas, 1706-1758; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Harvey, Thomas)
  - Haskins, Hanniball, 1696; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Haskins, Hanniball)
  - Haughton, ? (minor), 1727; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Haughton, ? (minor))
  - Haughton, Thomas, n.d.; CCR 199; Colonial Courts (Folder Haughton, Thomas)
  - Hawkins, John, 1719-1727; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hawkins, John)
  - Hawkins, Sarah, 1725-1727; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hawkins, Sarah)
  - Hawkins, Thomas, 1696; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hawkins, Thomas)
  - Hawkins, Thomas Leget, 1743-1744; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hawkins, Thomas Leget)
  - Hawks, Seth, 1727; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hawks, Seth)
  - Hawstead, Thomas and Ann, 1717-1722; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hawstead, Thomas and Ann)
  - Haynes, Roger, 1739-1742; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Haynes, Roger)
  - Hecklefield, John (see Edmund and Mary Gale), 1721-1740; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hecklefield, John (see Edmund and Mary Gale))
  - Henderson, David, 1735-1745; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Henderson, David)
  - Henderson, George, 1736-1744; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Henderson, George)
  - Henley, Patrick, 1700; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Henley, Patrick)
  - Hernet, Cornelius, 1743; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hernet, Cornelius)
  - Hick, David, 1733; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hick, David)
  - Hicks, Affrica, 1712; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hicks, Affrica)
  - Hicks, Thomas, 1724-1728; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hicks, Thomas)
  - Hill, Henry, 1722; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hill, Henry)
  - Hill, Samuel, 1722; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hill, Samuel)
  - Hill, Thomas, 1708-1734; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hill, Thomas)
  - Hinton, John, 1732; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hinton, John)
  - Hocot, Edward, 1755-1757; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hocot, Edward)
  - Hodges, Robert, 1757-1758; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hodges, Robert)
  - Hodgson, John, 1746-1759; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hodgson, John)
  - Holbrook (Hollbrook), John, 1743-1746; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Holbrook (Hollbrook), John)
  - Holladay (Holliday), Thomas, 1737-1746; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Holladay (Holliday), Thomas)
  - Hollowell, Thomas, 1743-1744; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hollowell, Thomas)
  - Holt, Martin, 1738; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Holt, Martin)
  - Hope, Henry, 1741-1743; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hope, Henry)
  - Hopper, Davie, 1736-1744; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hopper, Davie)
  - Howley, Lawrence, 1741; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Howley, Lawrence)
  - Hudson, William, 1702; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hudson, William)
  - Hunt, Christopher, 1741-1742; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hunt, Christopher)
  - Hunt, John, Capt., 1712; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hunt, John, Capt.)
  - Hunter, James, 1743; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hunter, James)
  - Hunter, Thomas, 1739-1757; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hunter, Thomas)
  - Hyde, Edward, 1711-1713; CCR 200; Colonial Courts (Folder Hyde, Edward)
  - Ingram, Roger, 1745-1746; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Ingram, Roger)
  - Irby, Hannah, 1734; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Irby, Hannah)
  - Irby, Henry, 1733-1739; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Irby, Henry)
  - Isnard, Claudius, 1740; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Isnard, Claudius)
  - Jack, Alexander, 1745-1758; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Jack, Alexander)
  - Jackson, Benjamin, 1735-1736; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Jackson, Benjamin)
  - Jackson, David, 1730; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Jackson, David)
  - Jaspar, Richard, 1722-1743; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Jaspar, Richard)
  - Jeffereys, Simon, Capt., 1732-1743; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Jeffereys, Simon, Capt.)
  - Jefferys, William, n.d.; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Jefferys, William)
  - Jenings, Ann, 1715-1724; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Jenings, Ann)
  - Jenner, James, 1736; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Jenner, James)
  - Jesop, Thomas, 1753-1758; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Jesop, Thomas)
  - Jewell, Thomas, 1736-1737; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Jewell, Thomas)
  - Johnson, James, 1694; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Johnson, James)
  - Johnson, John, 1723-1726; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Johnson, John)
  - Johnston, Benjamin, 1742; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Johnston, Benjamin)
  - Jones, Charles, 1695; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Jones, Charles)
  - Jones, Daniell, n.d.; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Jones, Daniell)
  - Jones, John, 1723; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Jones, John)
  - Jones, John, 1760; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Jones, John)
  - Jones, Robert, n.d.; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Jones, Robert)
  - Jones, Thomas, 1709-1755; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Jones, Thomas)
  - Jones, William, 1723; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Jones, William)
  - Jones, William Harding, 1734; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Jones, William Harding)
  - Jordan, Solomon, 1723; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Jordan, Solomon)
  - Keaten, John, 1736; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Keaten, John)
  - Keefe, Treddell, 1723-1726; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Keefe, Treddell)
  - Kenyon, Roger, 1731-1737; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Kenyon, Roger)
  - Ketchmaid, ? (see also Catchmaid), 1694-1695; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Ketchmaid, ? (see also Catchmaid))
  - Killingsworth, Richard, 1734-1739; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Killingsworth, Richard)
  - King, Henry, 1717; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder King, Henry)
  - Kippin, Walter, 1756-1757; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Kippin, Walter)
  - Knight, Tobias, 1715-1728; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Knight, Tobias)
  - Lafitte, Timothy, 1743-1746; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Lafitte, Timothy)
  - Laker, Benjamin, 1701; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Laker, Benjamin)
  - Lamb, Joshua, n.d.; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Lamb, Joshua)
  - Langstone, Thomas, n.d.; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Langstone, Thomas)
  - Lardner, Henry, 1733; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Lardner, Henry)
  - Larson, Lawrence, 1744; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Larson, Lawrence)
  - Lary, ? (Widdow?), n.d.; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Lary, ? (Widdow?))
  - Latham, Paul, 1694; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Latham, Paul)
  - Lawley, David, 1729-1735; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Lawley, David)
  - Lawson, John, 1712-1713; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Lawson, John)
  - Lear, John, Col. and Anna, 1694-1700; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Lear, John, Col. and Anna)
  - Lee, Thomas, 1753-1757; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Lee, Thomas)
  - LePelle, Hillary, 1744; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder LePelle, Hillary)
  - Lerry, Cornelius, n.d.; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Lerry, Cornelius)
  - Lewis, Adam, n.d.; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Lewis, Adam)
  - Lide, Sarah (widow), 1744; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Lide, Sarah (widow))
  - Lightfoot, Francis, 1727-1732; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Lightfoot, Francis)
  - Lillington, Alexander, 1697; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Lillington, Alexander)
  - Linsay, Robert, 1690; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Linsay, Robert)
  - Linscomb, John, 1738-1742; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Linscomb, John)
  - Little, William, 1735-1744; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Little, William)
  - Logan, Alexander, 1740-1744; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Logan, Alexander)
  - Long, James, 1711; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Long, James)
  - Long, Mary, 1693; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Long, Mary)
  - Loster, William, 1746; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Loster, William)
  - Love, Edward, 1757-1758; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Love, Edward)
  - Lovick, John, 1733; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Lovick, John)
  - Low, Emanuel, 1742; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Low, Emanuel)
  - Lowry, Robert, 1757-1758; CCR 201; Colonial Courts (Folder Lowry, Robert)
  - MacCray, Robert, 1738-1741; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder MacCray, Robert)
  - Mackey, Ann (minor), 1717-1718; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Mackey, Ann (minor))
  - Mackey, Daniel, 1697; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Mackey, Daniel)
  - Mague, Lawrence, 1741; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Mague, Lawrence)
  - Manwaring, Hannah (minor), n.d.; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Manwaring, Hannah (minor))
  - Stephen Manwaring, 1699; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Stephen Manwaring)
  - Marsden, Richard, 1740-1743; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Marsden, Richard)
  - Marsden, Thomas, 1737-1740; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Marsden, Thomas)
  - Martin, George, 1735; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Martin, George)
  - Martin, John, 1739-1742; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Martin, John)
  - Massechoes, Benjamin, n.d.; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Massechoes, Benjamin)
  - Mathews, William, 1742-1746; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Mathews, William)
  - Mathias, John, 1737; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Mathias, John)
  - Maudlin, Ezekiel, 1738; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Maudlin, Ezekiel)
  - Maule, Patrick, 1736-1737; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Maule, Patrick)
  - Maule, William, Col., 1722-1730; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Maule, William, Col.)
  - Maund, William, CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Maund, William)
  - Maxwell, William (see also Cornelius Harnet), 1734-1745; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Maxwell, William (see also Cornelius Harnet))
  - Mayo, Em, 1707; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Mayo, Em)
  - McAdams, James, 1742-1744; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder McAdams, James)
  - McClendon, Dennis, 1733-1736; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder McClendon, Dennis)
  - McClure, Richard, 1753; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder McClure, Richard)
  - McGregor, Patrick and Gregor, 1718; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder McGregor, Patrick and Gregor)
  - McNeil, Dugald, 1743; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder McNeil, Dugald)
  - Meade, Andrew, 1745; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Meade, Andrew)
  - Meade, David, 1754-1759; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Meade, David)
  - Merrick, Thomas, 1741-1744; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Merrick, Thomas)
  - Mieds, Timothy, 1741-1755; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Mieds, Timothy)
  - Millikin, James, 1737-1745; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Millikin, James)
  - Mitchell, James, 1742-1746; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Mitchell, James)
  - Mitchell, John, 1718-1724; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Mitchell, John)
  - Mitchell, William, 1723-1726; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Mitchell, William)
  - Montgomery, John and Ann, 1745-1747; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Montgomery, John and Ann)
  - Moore, Andrew, 1758; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Moore, Andrew)
  - Moore (More), Edward, 1736-1737; CCR 202; Colonial Courts (Folder Moore (More), Edward)
  - Morgan, James, 1714; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Morgan, James)
  - Morgan, John, 1734-1737; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Morgan, John)
  - Mott, Stephen, 1735-1739; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Mott, Stephen)
  - Mowbery, William, 1700; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Mowbery, William)
  - Mulkey, John, 1741; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Mulkey, John)
  - Mulkey, Philip, 1737-1742; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Mulkey, Philip)
  - Munden, Stephen, CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Munden, Stephen)
  - Muns, Thomas, n.d.; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Muns, Thomas)
  - Murphy, William, 1737; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Murphy, William)
  - Nairn, John, 1739-1740; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Nairn, John)
  - Nayler, Richard, 1677-1696; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Nayler, Richard)
  - Niccolson, Benjamin, 1706; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Niccolson, Benjamin)
  - Nicolson, Joseph, 1698; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Nicolson, Joseph)
  - Nixon, John, 1739; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Nixon, John)
  - Nixon, Richard, 1736-1741; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Nixon, Richard)
  - Norcombe, Thomas, 1703; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Norcombe, Thomas)
  - Norman, Henry, n.d.; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Norman, Henry)
  - Northcoat, John, n.d.; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Northcoat, John)
  - Northy, David, 1711-1730; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Northy, David)
  - Oakman, Samuel, 1738-1745; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Oakman, Samuel)
  - O'Daniel, Owen, 1738; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder O'Daniel, Owen)
  - Odum, Richard, 1730-1744; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Odum, Richard)
  - Ormond, Wyriot, 1757-1766; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Ormond, Wyriot)
  - Ormondy, John, 1720-1723; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Ormondy, John)
  - Orrell, John, 1726; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Orrell, John)
  - Outlaw, Edward, 1736-1742; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Outlaw, Edward)
  - Overington, Robert, 1753; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Overington, Robert)
  - Owen, William, 1738-1740; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Owen, William)
  - Packe (Parke), Richard, 1737; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Packe (Parke), Richard)
  - Pagiter, William, 1721-1728; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Pagiter, William)
  - Palin, Henry, 1701-1716; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Palin, Henry)
  - Palin, James, 1724; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Palin, James)
  - Parker, Richard, 1753; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Parker, Richard)
  - Parker, Thomas, 1718; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Parker, Thomas)
  - Parker, Thomas, 1752; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Parker, Thomas)
  - Parks, William, 1756-1757; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Parks, William)
  - Parris, Thomas, 1728; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Parris, Thomas)
  - Partridge, Nathaniel, 1738; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Partridge, Nathaniel)
  - Patterson, Robert, 1719-1724; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Patterson, Robert)
  - Payne, Peter, 1756; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Payne, Peter)
  - Payton, Robert, 1739-1743; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Payton, Robert)
  - Peade, Timothy, n.d.; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Peade, Timothy)
  - Peirce, Thomas, 1737-1744; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Peirce, Thomas)
  - Pendleton, Henry, 1740; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Pendleton, Henry)
  - Perry, George, 1736; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Perry, George)
  - Perry, Jeremiah, 1707; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Perry, Jeremiah)
  - Peterson, Jacob, n.d.; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Peterson, Jacob)
  - Phelps, Edward, 1721; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Phelps, Edward)
  - Phillips, John, Capt., 1735-1741; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Phillips, John, Capt.)
  - Phillpott, John, 1694-1697; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Phillpott, John)
  - Pilson, Thomas, 1743-1745; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Pilson, Thomas)
  - Plater, Richard, 1706; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Plater, Richard)
  - Plowman, John, 1719-1726; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Plowman, John)
  - Pointavinte, Peter, 1742; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Pointavinte, Peter)
  - Pointavinte, Samuel, 1735-1744; CCR 203; Colonial Courts (Folder Pointavinte, Samuel)
  - Pollock, Cullen, 1735-1758; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Pollock, Cullen)
  - Pollock, George, 1734-1744; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Pollock, George)
  - Pollock, Thomas, 1722-1723; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Pollock, Thomas)
  - Pordage, George, 1698-1702; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Pordage, George)
  - Porter, John, 1709-1713; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Porter, John)
  - Porter, John, 1743-1746; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Porter, John)
  - Porter, Joshua, 1736-1737; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Porter, Joshua)
  - Power, John, 1738-1740; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Power, John)
  - Powers, George, 1696; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Powers, George)
  - Pratt, John, 1743; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Pratt, John)
  - Price, Thomas, 1696; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Price, Thomas)
  - Prichet, David, 1757; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Prichet, David)
  - Pugh, Francis, 1736-1744; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Pugh, Francis)
  - Pugh, John, 1738-1756; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Pugh, John)
  - Pugh, Theophilus, 1741-1759; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Pugh, Theophilus)
  - Relph, Thomas, n.d.; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Relph, Thomas)
  - Ramsay, John, 1721-1741; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Ramsay, John)
  - Randall, Thomas, 1724; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Randall, Thomas)
  - Rasbury, John, 1736-1757; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Rasbury, John)
  - Ratcliff, Samuel, n.d.; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Ratcliff, Samuel)
  - Rawlins, Benjamin, 1740; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Rawlins, Benjamin)
  - Reed, Samuel, 1739-1742; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Reed, Samuel)
  - Reed, William, 1728-1755; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Reed, William)
  - Reston, Thomas, 1724-1725; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Reston, Thomas)
  - Reynaud, Benjamin, 1714; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Reynaud, Benjamin)
  - Richards, Mary, 1743; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Richards, Mary)
  - Richardson, John, 1742-1745; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Richardson, John)
  - Rieusset, John, 1738-1743; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Rieusset, John)
  - Rigby, William, 1744; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Rigby, William)
  - Rigen, Daniel, 1743-1744; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Rigen, Daniel)
  - Rigg,William, 1744; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Rigg,William)
  - Riggin, John, 1700; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Riggin, John)
  - Rigney, John, 1727-1739; CCR 204; Colonial Courts (Folder Rigney, John)
  - Roberts, Benjamin, 1737; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Roberts, Benjamin)
  - Robbins, James, 1725; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Robbins, James)
  - Robinson, Cotton, 1707-1723; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Robinson, Cotton)
  - Rogers, Emanuel, 1729; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Rogers, Emanuel)
  - Rose, Sarah (minor), 1713-1714; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Rose, Sarah (minor))
  - Roper, Thomas, 1721-1724; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Roper, Thomas)
  - Ross. William, 1722-1724; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Ross. William)
  - Rowan, Thomas, 1738-1745; CCR 205; Colonial Courts (Folder Rowan, Thomas)